export const MongodbQuizData = [
    {
      title: "MongoDB",
      question: "What type of NoSQL database is MongoDB?",
      options: [
        "Document-oriented",
        "Key-value",
        "Column-family",
        "Graph-based"
      ],
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      title: "MongoDB",
      question: "What is BSON in MongoDB?",
      options: [
        "Binary Script Object Notation",
        "Binary Style Object Notation",
        "Binary Serialized Object Notation",
        "Binary JSON"
      ],
      answer: 4
    },
    {
      title: "MongoDB",
      question: "Which command is used to create a new database in MongoDB?",
      options: [
        "create db",
        "new db",
        "use db",
        "db.create()"
      ],
      answer: 3
    },
    {
      title: "MongoDB",
      question: "What is the primary key in MongoDB called?",
      options: [
        "_id",
        "ObjectId",
        "PrimaryId",
        "key"
      ],
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      title: "MongoDB",
      question: "Which operator is used for querying documents in MongoDB?",
      options: [
        "find",
        "search",
        "query",
        "select"
      ],
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      title: "MongoDB",
      question: "What is sharding in MongoDB?",
      options: [
        "Creating a backup of the database",
        "Distributing data across multiple machines",
        "Encrypting data in the database",
        "Renaming a collection"
      ],
      answer: 2
    },
    {
      title: "MongoDB",
      question: "Which method is used to update documents in MongoDB?",
      options: [
        "update",
        "modify",
        "change",
        "edit"
      ],
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      title: "MongoDB",
      question: "What does the term 'replica set' mean in MongoDB?",
      options: [
        "A set of similar documents",
        "A set of backup databases",
        "A set of synchronized MongoDB instances",
        "A set of database operations"
      ],
      answer: 3
    },
    {
      title: "MongoDB",
      question: "How can you perform an aggregation in MongoDB?",
      options: [
        "aggregate() method",
        "group() method",
        "sort() method",
        "merge() method"
      ],
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      title: "MongoDB",
      question: "Which command is used to remove documents from a collection in MongoDB?",
      options: [
        "delete",
        "remove",
        "erase",
        "discard"
      ],
      answer: 2
    },
    {
      title: "MongoDB",
      question: "What is the default port number for MongoDB?",
      options: [
        "27017",
        "8080",
        "3306",
        "5432"
      ],
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      title: "MongoDB",
      question: "What does the term 'Index' mean in MongoDB?",
      options: [
        "A collection of documents",
        "A sorted data structure that improves query performance",
        "A type of document",
        "A backup of the database"
      ],
      answer: 2
    },
    {
      title: "MongoDB",
      question: "Which method is used to limit the number of documents returned in a query?",
      options: [
        "limit()",
        "count()",
        "skip()",
        "limitRows()"
      ],
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      title: "MongoDB",
      question: "How can you sort the results of a query in descending order in MongoDB?",
      options: [
        "desc()",
        "descending()",
        "sortDesc()",
        "sort()"
      ],
      answer: 4
    },
    {
      title: "MongoDB",
      question: "What is GridFS in MongoDB?",
      options: [
        "A file system",
        "A graph database",
        "A distributed database",
        "A data modeling technique"
      ],
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      title: "MongoDB",
      question: "Which data type is used to store large files in MongoDB?",
      options: [
        "Blob",
        "File",
        "GridFS",
        "LargeData"
      ],
      answer: 3
    },
    {
      title: "MongoDB",
      question: "What is the purpose of the 'db.collection.stats()' method in MongoDB?",
      options: [
        "Display statistics about a collection",
        "Create a new collection",
        "Remove a collection",
        "Update a collection"
      ],
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      title: "MongoDB",
      question: "Which method is used to create an index in MongoDB?",
      options: [
        "addIndex()",
        "createIndex()",
        "index()",
        "buildIndex()"
      ],
      answer: 2
    },
    {
      title: "MongoDB",
      question: "What is the role of the 'mongod' process in MongoDB?",
      options: [
        "Query processing",
        "Data storage",
        "Replication",
        "Data migration"
      ],
      answer: 2
    },
    {
      title: "MongoDB",
      question: "How can you connect to a MongoDB server using the MongoDB shell?",
      options: [
        "connect() method",
        "use() method",
        "mongo() method",
        "mongod() method"
      ],
      answer: 3
    }
  ];
  